The bachelor turns off a phone,
relaxes his lips, relaxes them,
develops a small smile, relaxes them, strengthens his
stomach, unfortunately not 10,
relaxes his eyelids,
relaxes his fingers,
then directs his attention to his
breath, counts ten, long exhales,
please, expensive lama to come and place a medal,
his body was allowed to, even with closed eyes,
can you smell the scent
of morality,
they admired their beauty
and something specific about
them,
this corresponds to a mental
bow, and
then think of something good you did
yesterday or a
small realization you had yesterday,
quite specifically that you did something good yesterday
or a great idea you
had,
then something goes, did you do something bad, have
bad habits, 2
intensely,
and then promises them in your mind
not to do it again, and that helps you stop,
and then please look at yourself, teach yourself
now, if you sometimes, if you are
not necessarily worth it,
ask them to stay in a life,
and then think about the years of life
that you might still want to stay, give me
a number, maybe ten or 15 years,
maybe 20, try to imagine
how many  The years that remain are
assumed to be 20 years, and
you spend a third of them sleeping, a
third or a quarter carrying things around,
that leaves only 15 years.
15 years awake,
and you spend two hours a day of
those 15 years cooking and
eating. Now we have to subtract the cooking time,
then you have to
subtract another 15 percent, leaving us with
twelve years.
And then you have to go shopping, have to
shower,
then there are still things to do,
and then you have to go to work to
pay the rent, to pay for food,
leaving eight years.
Then you have obligations to your
family; you have to spend time with your
parents and other
family members because otherwise you're
not a good person.
Then there are six years left.
My friends also need some time;
I have to talk to my friends. To have
friends, I have to pay
attention to what moves them.
Four years left,
and then I send out emails on the
internet, what happens on the
website Facebook?
Then we have two years left in
my life to spend the rest of my
Real time in life to practice, to
meditate,
to expect the apprenticeship, we have
two more years,
that's all I have.
It's so hard to find blocks of time
in the 20 minutes here, so hard
to find free time on vacation to meditate, to
do my book, to study, so little
time.
We stay a few minutes
and then take three deep breaths
slowly, could
open your eyes again, stretch, good, good
meditation. He was very quiet. It's a
good group of meditators.
I'll give you a note, maybe
tomorrow, with the reasons why he should do the
death meditation. I did
n't expect we'd get this far,
but it really went too fast.
I'll just briefly repeat them in Guadalajara:
the three basic principles. The first is that
it's certain you have to die,
and there are three reasons for this.
The first is in the text; in the original text, it says
the master of death will
come one hundred percent, and there's
nothing that can stop him, no
medicine, no matter
where you go, no matter how strong you
are. The second reason is that death
is certain;
you can't add time to a
lifetime.  Add to that the fact that
time flies,
you can't stop it, that's
the second reason. The third reason,
we just did it, even with
the time I have left,
you don't have time to practice because it's
so busy to get a few hours of
retreat. It's really
difficult;
you work for months, you have to travel from far away.
I don't know,
in the yogic theory of digestion, it's like eating
a donut, and then it goes into
the stomach and it's processed,
and the essence of a donut is then
really just a drop, a real
food maybe. And with your time,
practicing like that is the same. To be
able to practice for an hour, you
have very little time to make music. That's why, for example,
if you're
Black, if you discover a moment,
ask how you finished back then. I
have all that,
I have all that, you know, days to that.
Reason 456, the first one,
that's the fourth reason.
The things that can kill you are
many, the things that keep you alive
are fewer. Sometimes
I think the world is a tactical mandala
because I think there isn't that
much.  Place a green drink and so
much spinach in it again, there should
actually be miles and hedges and hectares
of spinach fields. Spinach
only grows in a few places; in
most places, spinach grows. But
the things that will kill you are
everywhere.
Now we're at reason number 6.
Reason number six is ​​being full. Third reason
why you don't know that the body
is very fragile. It's about you having a
560 Chevy. We have songs about
how these cars are now 60
years old, this one younger than me, and they're all
falling apart.
All these services are already falling apart.
But I have muscle, and it's really, really, really
hard
to find a body.
I found one, then shortly
after, didn't sell it because it just
fell apart.
The brakes didn't work at that time,
but your body is still
working, still working, and that's what
we're talking about. Now you're done.
No problem.
You can look for Alois Luschin; she
has real coffee. If you die, it
's uncertain because your body
is so fragile. It means
fragile in the  In colloquial language,
we're now making a dictionary. "Eindrang"
means shy, so
it really means very shy.
Here, it means fragile, very, very
fragile.
Even if it means there are many things that
can harm you, and only a
few that keep you alive,
but if our body were like what's the
good guy in the Transformers movie,
if we had such a body, then
it would be cool if there were many things
that could kill us and the ceiling would fall
under. So, if we
had such a body, then it would be okay if there were
so many things around us that
could kill us. But, but,
but our body is like a water
bubble in the bathtub.
If a cactus thorn pricks you, and
if you can't get out, it can
kill you.
I rather think that
Abraham Lincoln's son died like that; he
simply pricked himself on one
and it became infected. And Lama
Annika
fell into a cactus during the first year retreat
and she had a [condition] for three years.  I had a
swollen hand that never
healed, just a small prick.
Our body isn't like this
Transformer; it doesn't take much to
kill a monk's human body.
You can go anywhere. What's the name of that great
restaurant on top of a casino in
Singapore? It's a French
restaurant.
I spent a month's salary there.
Anyway,
you can
get a salmonella infection that
kills you in the best restaurant in
Singapore.
Even if our body were like this
dance form, then it's like
having armor. If it were so super protected
and solid,
what is a sitting pest? The letter to
a friend, send a letter and
Galliani with a king-size letter.
That's what the surface of our
planet Earth is called.
That's what the big mountains are like: Mount
Everest and K2. They are the big ones,
several: the Pacific Ocean, the
Indian Ocean, and there will come a time, according to
Dahmer's third chapter, when
the sun goes supernova. And that's normal;
all stars will
explode eventually. And in the Abi Dame, it says
that this star, which we call the sun,
then...  Just before it perishes,
it will have 100 percent more power,
and lights will have 200 percent more
energy. That's the supernova, and then
in the pot, and then it will probably become
a black hole.
They call it the Days of the Seven Suns.
When our sun explodes, that's
really great grief.
All the trees will dry up and
then go up in flames.
People will die young, the seas will dry up,
the mountains will melt, and then the earth will melt and
then
the earth will dissolve into nothingness, and then the sun will become
a black hole. Even
Mount Paris will melt, and
here, "remains" means even if
the topic doesn't remain.
So, if you grind Mount Everest to dust, even
the dust
dissolves and nothing remains, then
this fragile body will be more...
Who will even talk about this
fragile body then? Even if you
have this transformer body, even
if you were wearing armor, all
things...  On this earth,
several mountains will dissolve. Okay, who
then speaks about your body? It has to be yourself.
Who then even has to
speak about it? Do I even have to mention it?
Many of these quotes are from the
same book.
Life is full of dangers.
Our body is like a bubble.
The connection is driven when
children make soap bubbles.
How long does it take for them to burst? And
our body is nothing else.
You know, whether it's just to inhale,
and the option is exhale. It's breath.
I want you to subside again. In
the Abi Dame, there is a
preparatory exercise for meditation,
and it's called inhale, exhale, inhale, exhale.
And in countries like Burma and
Thailand,
the only Buddhism that
got there is the Dame. All the
other books about empty, haid, mind. Only the mind
school in China has received the middle
way and mind, but of
the five great books, only the
Dame went there, and that's why
the theater meditation is so well-known and
famous.
This is the first meditation I
learned before  For 100 years,
everything they do is
breathtaking. It's good, it's
good preparation, but it's like the
warm-up instead of running the race.
You don't train your whole life to
go to the Olympics
and do warm-ups instead of running
the race. And breath
meditation is also a warm-up.
Here it means exhaling and
inhaling, and here it means killing, but
without the pro and without the gray, it means
waking up from sleep.
So be careful when he
translates this.
Here it means waking up from sleep. Then
if you have the grace
to wake up from sleep again, then that's
incredible. The
fact that you wake up in the morning is an
incredible fact. There was
an old Jewish rabbi who was talking,
and others
asked, "Why are you so happy?" And
he answered, "I'm just glad
that I woke up today. This
morning, I didn't die today.
Why are you so happy? I
woke up again." And here Magath says,
snorting, "The same fact that you
woke up a lot today."  Isn't it no wonder
that there's still fear about
who makes your breath? All the scientists,
all the doctors, who
invest billions of dollars to
find out what caused the first breath.
We know that if you have karma, then you have something
to breathe. You
want to be the only person on the
Titanic
who survives. Then even an
iceberg can't kill you. If you do
n't have the karma to breathe, then
a cactus thorn will prick you and you
will die.
The scientists are so worried
about what caused the first
breath, and then it gives a
wonderful...
If you take one of those, then you take
back the basic physical form,
haha. Since the senses are balanced, winds
still go through your body with
a very reduced breath.
Only if your husband died is it
stronger, but most people are
almost no longer alive when they
sleep. Their breath hardly moves anymore.
The element of wind is raised to another
level,
but for these, time ends in the
pit. Breathing stops. It's incredible that
you don't die during this time.  This
exposed, physical being suspected that
it would return in the morning is
a miracle.
He doesn't have to; you could simply stop breathing.
But the fact that you continue breathing, that
you wake up, that you're back to physical
breathing
is a miracle.
I like this idea. Express me that they haven't
taught. It's wonderful. It
's not safe. If you die, the
exposed one—what's it called?—if you're like,
if you're in a lodge
and someone sent a message in
a food castle: in the next 24
hours, someone is coming who wants to kill you. Good
luck. It's someone coming in a
yurt in the next 24 hours to
kill you. Good luck. And you send you over
the counter to see if there's anything on
the back.
You would do something to be
ready,
so you'd set bear traps,
and you just make a water trap on the
door. So you would just
prepare.
If you know that someone is going to kill you, then
you wouldn't
wait until tomorrow. They're coming right now.
Night, but you would say
I don't do anything at the moment you write the
letter,
and what to do if you come, men,
but weren't, then it
should be, and I'll
relax later.
If you don't, if you don't
fall in the morning, then you can still
run in the afternoon. Afterwards, you can
still chat, and if you've been pushed,
if you fall, then you've done the right
thing, and if you don't stop,
you can still chat.
But our habit is, I'm working
on a project, I have clients,
I'm writing a book. I'll just
adjust the schedule accordingly. I'll
finish writing the book first, and
then I'll practice. After that,
I'll do the death meditation. It has to be
different, so do
your death meditation first so you
're prepared. If you die, write it,
finish the book later. If you don't die, then
you can finish the book afterwards. You
have to set priorities. Do a
meditation in the morning. What is York?
That knocks me off my feet.
Then you're on the safe side. If
you can't be, you can't. All the
others really do that,
but if you chat first...  And you
think you're meditating
afterwards, then you're deceiving yourself. You're still deceiving yourself.
Nobody's bothering you, you're deceiving
yourself. How long is the class? It's a
quarter past ten. I'll be there soon. There'll be a
short break, and then
we'll finish this, and then there'll be
a break.
She says she wants to meet a ghost. There's
a big debate in America. Do
ghosts exist? For 100 years, everyone still believed in
the devil, but few people
believe today. There's
a book that says the
devil's greatest achievement is that
nobody believes in him anymore. The
devil exists. The devil exists,
and it is. Ghosts exist. If you
meditate on a film, then you can meet demons.
What does it do there? Is it really fear? That
's another story.
I'm so busy. I have a
plan.
I am. I'm going to do a
really good retreat next year. I'm going to
start my book next month. I'm so busy now. I
still have a few things to finish,
and then I'm really going to...  I'm going to
start my book and then I'm going to do all
my death meditations. I'm going to
come to the mountain and
do a month of solo work,
really in 2017. But I have to finish a few
things beforehand, and then
I'll take care of it, and then
someone is going to come and take them behind a car
in the next 24 hours. So that's why
it's better to take care of it now.
Do a death meditation, do
your retreat now, do some yoga,
meditate,
and if you don't fall, then you can
do all the other things. When you
die, then you're ready, like a
daughter or a son
returning to their parents' house. You're ready.
Okay, I asked when it's going to start.
You're not afraid. When you're ready, then
it's really strange. You just say, "
I'm ready, come on, let's go, I
'm ready." He says the chip. If you
want to meet a real demon, then it's
this idea that you
practice later, that you have to take
care of a few other things now, and then
you'll take up a serious practice.
Then you're deceiving yourself.
How do you say that?  You're lying to your own
face again, and to understand that,
you first have to understand something else.
I lived with my teacher for 25 years,
and the first thing he did was watch
the news on TV,
and he had tweezers because we wo
n't have them later. They're
really lucky. We have to go through it
every day.
Scott always had to be out of his shell in the war,
but the Tibetans,
he's so lucky. And one day
we were debating,
what are you doing there, a debate? Yes,
but I've never seen anyone with hair.
Okay, so we believe I'm doing my
practice, on which I've finished all these things
I have to do, and
the same lama, the things you still
want to finish, the projects, the
sun, completely finished,
it's like the hair of an old
man, real, the older you get, the
faster it will grow. You know that we
older ones know that in the hand, like the
hair of an old man, which really
grows fast,
Lutz, it's out, and then they're back again.
You cut and
cut.  "Es ging" means present participle,
so you cut, you cut, and
cut is... but what is he talking about?
The things you still have to do before you
can practice... it's like a hair
from an old time, whether it's there or not, and it
's more... another project, and doing a
project, and another project, and another thing that has to be
done... it grows
and grows and grows...
we're taking a break now, especially for my
10-15 minutes.